・（美也）
にぃに　にぃに　起きてる？→
Nii-nii!
Nii-nii, are you up yet?
You're gonna be late!
遅刻するよ
（美也）どうしたの？　その顔
もしかして寝てないの？
What's wrong?  You look terrible!
Don't tell me you didn't get any sleep!
（純一）寝られなかった…
I couldn't sleep.
You look terrible.
（梅原）ひっでえ顔してんな　お前
（薫）あんた大丈夫？
Are you okay?
ほっといてくれ
Leave me alone.
いや　ホントひどいぞ　冗談抜きで
No, you really look terrible.  I'm not kidding.
ホントに　ひどい
ひどすぎるわよ　あんたの顔
It's really bad.  You look really bad.
Tachibana-kun, what's wrong?
（詞）橘君どうしたの？　保健室へ
行った方がいいんじゃない？
You should go rest in the infirmary.
先生には私から言っておくから
I'll let the teacher know.
Ahh...
ああ…　じゃあ　そうしようかな
I guess I'll do that.
Infirmary
Excuse me.
Huh?  The nurse isn't around?
Well, whatever.
I'm borrowing a bed.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
（薫・梅原）ああ…
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
失礼しま～す
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
あれッ　先生いないのか
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
まあいいや　ベッド借りま～す
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
おッ
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
（はるか）う～ん
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
あッ…
・～
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
〈なッ　何で森島先輩がここに？〉
W-Why is Morishima-senpai here?
《僕　森島先輩のことが好きです》
I like you, Morishima-senpai.
I see.
《そうなんだ　ふ～ん》
Hmm.
《うん　ちょっと
ビックリしちゃった》
You kinda surprised me.
But no.
《でもダメ　私　年上で
頼りがいのある人が好みなの》
I prefer someone who's reliable and older than me.
う～ん…
Huh?  Tachibana-kun?
あれッ　橘君？
あッ　すッ　すみません
S-Sorry.
何で謝るの？
ああ　いや　だって…
Why are you apologizing?
Ah, well, I mean... I uh...
それは　その…
What are you doing in the infirmary?
保健室で　どうしたの？
どこか具合でも悪い？
Are you not feeling well?
あッ　ちょっと寝不足で
調子が悪くて…
I-I didn't really get enough sleep, so I'm not feeling too well...
そうなんだ　私も昨日
おもしろい深夜番組があって
I see.
I stayed up late yesterday too, because there was this interesting late night show on TV.
夜更かししちゃって　それで
ベッドを借りてたの　一緒だね
So I borrowed a bed.
Just like you!
そッ　そうですね　一緒ですね
ハハハ…
Y-Yeah.  Just like me.
〈うん？　森島先輩
何でこんなに普通なんだ？〉
Huh?
Why is Morishima-senpai acting so normally?
〈昨日　僕フラれたよな？〉
Didn't she reject me yesterday?
どうかしたの？
ちょっと君らしくないかも
What's the matter?
You don't really seem like yourself.
Ah... well, I'm a little surprised...
ああッ　その
ちょっと驚いちゃって…
Hmm?  About what?
うん？　何に？
いやッ　その…
Well, I mean...
その　先輩が
普通に今までと変わらないから
You're no different from how you usually are...
僕　先輩にフラれたのに…
Even though you rejected me...
Huh?
えッ？
ですから　僕は昨日　先輩に
I mean, you completely rejected me yesterday,
きっぱりフラれたのに　こうして
普通に話したりしていいのかなと
so I'm wondering if it's okay for us to talk like we normally do.
何で？
えッ？
Why?
Huh?
私　人づきあいって
彼氏彼女だけじゃないと思うの
I don't think you have to be in
a relationship to get along with others.
はあ？
実は結構　君のこと
I'm actually quite interested in you.
気に入っているんだけど　迷惑？
えッ？
Does it bother you?
〈うッ…　これは
どういうことなんだ？〉
What's this supposed to mean?
I see.
そっか　そうだよね
I guess so.
I'm sorry.  Even if I'm fine with it, I guess you're not.
ゴメンね　私はよくても
君はイヤだったよね
響にいつも怒られるんだ
もっと人の気持ちを思いやれって
Hibiki always gets mad at me for that.
She keeps telling me to be more considerate.
ゴメンね　無神経に話しかけて
迷惑だったよね
I'm sorry for talking to you so insensitively.
I must've bothered you.
T-That's not true at all!
そんなことないです
えッ？
逆に　僕から話しかけたら迷惑かと
思っていたくらいですから
In fact, I was thinking that you'd be bothered if I talked to you.
そうだったの？
はい
Really?
Yes.
Well, are you fine with us continuing to get along?
じゃあ　これからもよろしくで
いいのかな？
Y-Yes!  Let's get along!
はッ　はい　こちらこそ
よろしくお願いします
Good!  That's a good answer.
グッド！　よいお返事ね
U-Um, Senpai...
あッ　あの　先輩
うん？
Hmm?
一つ聞いていいですか？
何？
Can I ask you one thing?
What is it?
先輩の好みの男性って
You said that you prefer an older, reliable guy yesterday.
昨日　年上で頼りがいがある人って
聞きましたけど　その…
But... is there anything else you look for?
他には何かありますか？
私　そんなこと言ったっけ？
Huh?  Did I say that?
Didn't you?
違うんですか？
う～ん　タイプか～
Hmm, my type of guy, huh?
そうね　やっぱり
Let's see...
I guess I'd be attracted to a tough guy.
タフな男の人には憧れるかも
タフ？
Tough?
A guy who looks like he'd protect me no matter what.
何があっても守ってくれそうな
感じの人とか
あとはカリスマ性を
感じるような人もいいかも
A charismatic guy wouldn't be bad either.
カリスマ？
それにグッと周りをひきつける
Charismatic?
Or maybe someone who fascinates those around him,
魅力があって
リーダーシップがある人とか
a charming guy with leadership skills...
Leadership?
リーダーシップ？
あッ　でも
Ah, but I also get the feeling none of them are it.
どれも違うような気がしてきた
そんな～
You're kidding...
But I guess people like that are pretty amazing.
でもやっぱり
そういう人は素敵かも
Well, I've slept enough.
じゃ　私は十分寝たから
橘君もゆっくり休んでいってね
Tachibana-kun, be sure to rest well too.
あッ　はい…
Okay.
Morishima Haruka Arc
Chapter 2
Approach
You look a lot better now for some crazy reason.
何かメチャクチャ顔色よくなってない？
気持ち悪いぜ　どうした大将？
You're creeping me out.  What happened, boss?
ヘヘヘ…
I'm so glad.
〈よかった　これからも先輩と話が
できる　今までどおりでいいんだ〉
I can continue to talk to Morishima-senpai.
It'd be nice if things stayed the way they are.
〈いや　もしかしたら　もっと
仲良くなれるかもしれない〉
No, actually, we might get even closer to each other.
All right, I'm giving it all I've got!
よ～し　頑張るぞ　うお～ッ！
（子供Ａ）何だ？　あれ
（子供Ｂ）加速装置？
What's that?
A bionic accelerator?
はあ～
あッ　フフッ　かわいい～
So cute!
Sign: A new family member has arrived
あッ　このワンちゃん
あの子に似てるかも
This puppy kinda looks like him.
フフッ　顔　真っ赤にしちゃってさ
He was blushing so hard.
あのときの目は
ちょっとだけカッコよかったな
His eyes were just a little cool at that time.
うん　ちょっとだけね
Yep, just a little.
《》
《うお～ッ！》
《（ゴング）》
Ah, my bad.
（梅原）あッ　わりい
よけるなよ～
Don't dodge it!
あんなのまともに食らえるか
Like I'd just stand there and take it!
（紗江）あッ　あの人…
うん？→
Ah, that person...
Hmm?
にッ　にぃに！？
美也ちゃんの知ってる人？
N-Nii-nii?!
"Nii-nii"?  Miya-chan, do you know him?
えッ？　知らないよ
全然知らない人　見たことないし
N-No!  I don't know him.  I don't know him at all!
I've never seen him before either!
紗江ちゃん行こッ
S-Sae-chan, let's go!
何で　いきなりプロレスなんだ？
Why did you suddenly want to do pro wrestling?
僕は考えたんだ
タフ　カリスマ　リーダーシップ
I've been thinking.
Toughness.  Charisma.  Leadership.
これは　その全てを
手に入れるための特訓なんだ
This is intensive training for obtaining all of that.
And that's why you chose pro wrestling?
それでプロレスなのか？
いいから続けるぞ
Whatever, let's keep going!
ふんッ！
ずりい！　イテテ…
No fair!  Ow...
（はるか）あッ　おもしろそうね
私も　まぜてまぜて
Ah, that looks fun!
Let me play, let me play too!
M-Morishima-senpai?
森島先輩？
ウソ　マジ？　イテテ…
No way, seriously-
どうしてここに？
前の授業が体育だったの
What are you doing here?
My last class was P.E.
All right, bring it!
さあ　かかってきなさい
カモン　カモン
Come on, come on!
えッ　え～っと…
そう言われましても…
Uh, I don't know about that...
なあに　来ないの？
なら　こっちから技かけちゃうよ
What, you're not attacking?
Then I'll have to use my moves on you!
Like a Manji Hold!
卍固めとか
（純一・梅原）卍固め…
M... Manji Hold...
TL Note: A "Manji Hold" is a wrestling move with lots of body contact.
よろしくお願いします
（響）ちょっと　はるか→
Let's have a fair fight.
No fair!
Wait, Haruka.  What are you doing?
何やってるの？
響ちゃん
Hibiki-chan.
あら　この間の
Oh, you're the guy from before.
H-Hello.
どうも…
へッ？
そういえば
自己紹介が　まだだったわね
That reminds me, I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Tsukahara Hibiki, a senior.  Nice to meet you.
３年の塚原響よ　よろしくね
よろしくお願いします
Nice to meet you.
俺　梅原正吉っていいます
こいつの親友です
I'm Umehara Masayoshi.
I'm his best friend.
That's perfect!
響も来たことだし
２対２のタッグマッチにしましょう
Hibiki's here too, so let's have a two-on-two tag team match!
ファイッ！
・（響）「ファイッ！」じゃないでしょ
Fight!
What do you mean, "fight"?
All the equipment has been put away.
道具は片づけたんだから
早く着替えて帰るわよ
Hurry up and change so we can go home.
え～ッ　ヤダ
私もプロレスやりたい
Eh?  I don't wanna!
I want to do some pro wrestling!
I'm sorry she interfered.
邪魔して悪かったわね
続けてちょうだい
You can continue.
Uh...
え～っと…
あの…
Um...
僕達もそろそろ
終わりにしようかと　なあ？
We were just about to end it here too... right?
Yeah.
そうだな
え～ッ　残念
Really?  What a shame.
I'm sorry, maybe next time.
残念ですけど
またの機会ということで
むむむッ　絶対だよ
はい
Don't forget!
I won't.
しょうがないな　じゃあ
橘君達も一緒に帰りましょうか
It's too bad, I guess.
Well then, why don't we all go home together?
（純一・梅原）はあ？
これから帰るところなの
We're just about to go home.
いいでしょ？
私は別に構わないわ
You're fine with it, right?
I don't mind.
Both of you are okay with it too, right?
橘君達もオッケーよね？
（純一・梅原）う～ん…
Hmm...
はいッ　喜んで！
Yes, we'd be glad to!
Hey, Hibiki-chan...
〈みんな　こっち見てる…〉
Everyone's looking this way.
〈やっぱり森島先輩のことが
気になるのかな〉
It must be because of Morishima-senpai.
Hey, boss.
おいおい大将
今日はどんなラッキーデーだ？
Can you believe our luck?
森島先輩と一緒に帰れるなんて
うん…
We're walking home with Morishima-senpai!
Y-Yeah.
Walking home with Morishima-senpai.
〈森島先輩と一緒に帰れるなんて
これはすごい進歩だ　うん〉
That's a huge step forward.  Yep.
・（女子生徒）さようなら
・（はるか）さようなら
Bye, Morishima-senpai!
Bye!
・（先生）気をつけて
・（はるか）は～い
Take care on your way home.
I will!
森島先輩　すごい人気だな
（梅原）いまさら何言ってんだ
Morishima-senpai's really popular.
You just realized that?
I heard that Morishima-senpai
used to join one club after another.
何でも森島先輩
昔はいろんな部活に入っては
「何か違うな～」って
退部を繰り返してたらしいぜ
She'd say "something isn't right",
drop out, and then repeat the process.
That seems to be the secret to why she's so well-known.
それが　あの顔の広さの秘密らしい
へえ～
Normally you drift away from a club you've dropped out of,
普通は退部したら
疎遠になるとこなのに→
あのとおり
今でも仲はいいし慕われてもいる
but as you can see, they still get along with her and adore her.
I guess that's her charm.
それが先輩の魅力なのかな…
はるかのモテモテぶりは
それだけじゃないのよ
That's not the only reason why Haruka's popular.
聞いてたんですか？
聞こえてきたの
You were listening?
We could hear you.
Recently, the most popular guys from both the junior and senior year confessed to her at the same time.
この前なんて２年と３年の
一番モテるって男の子に
同時に告白されたんだから
告白？
Confessed?!
Oh, I remember hearing about that!
俺も聞いたことあります
（響）同じ日の同じ時間→
The same time, on the same day,
they called her out to different places.
別々の場所へ呼び出されて
断るのに校内を駆けまわって→
She had to run all over the school to turn them down.
忙しそうだったわ
She was busy.
〈断ったんだ　よかった…〉
So she turned them down...
Thank goodness.
（響）うらやましいわ　私も同級生や
後輩からラブレターをもらって→
I'm kinda jealous.
I'd like to receive love letters from
my classmate and my underclassman,
同じ日　同じ時間に
校内を駆けまわりたいものね
and run all over the school to meet them on the same time and day too.
（はるか）あれは　たまたまで…
もう　知ってるくせに
That was just a coincidence!
Geez, and you know it.
最近は　そんなこともなくて
ヒマでしょうがないくらいよ
Nothing like that has happened recently, and I'm getting really bored.
あら　じゃあ一人で女子水泳部の
活動をのぞくのもヒマだから？
Oh?
So you peek at the Girls Swim Club activities alone because you're bored?
That's because the girls are so cute when they're
hard at work, not knowing they're being watched!
だって　私に
のぞかれてるのも知らないで→
頑張ってる女の子達が
かわいいんだもん
That's totally sexual harassment.
（響）それ　完全なセクハラ発言よ
（梅原）あの
Excuse me.
そんなにモテるんだったら
今までフラれても→
Since you're that popular with the guys,
has anyone ever confessed to you again even after you rejected him?
また告白してきた人とか
いないんですか？
そういえば　いないわね
もし　してきたらどうします？
Now that you mention it, there hasn't.
What would you do if it happened?
You mean, if he confessed again?
もう一度　告白ってこと？
はい
Yes.
Let's see...
そうね…　そんな人いなかったから
分からないけど
It's never happened before, so I don't really know...
もう一度　断るんじゃないかな
そうですよね
But I guess I'd probably turn him down again.
I guess so.
（はるか）そのときにならないと
分からないけど
Though, I wouldn't know for sure until it happens.
（梅原）そんなヤツ　いないですよね
Nobody would try anyway.
I guess.  I've never heard of anyone confessing a second time.
（響）そうね　二度目の告白なんて
聞いたことないものね
And so, the feelings I swore that day crumbled all too easily.
〈こうして
あの日　誓った僕の思いは〉
〈簡単に打ち砕かれたのだった〉
・（美也）また　ひどい顔してる
You're looking terrible again.
もしかして　ゆうべ
みゃーが　にぃにの分まで
Is it because I ate your share of meat buns last night, Nii-nii?
まんま肉まん食べたから？
そうだよね　みゃーだったら
Though I understand.
I don't think I'd be able to sleep either if someone ate my share of meat buns.
自分のまんま肉まん食べられたら
夜も眠れないもん　ゴメンね
I'm sorry.
あッ　おはよう橘君　美也ちゃん
Morning, Tachibana-kun and Miya-chan!
Morishima-senpai, good morning!
森島先輩　おはようございます
どうも…
Hello.
フフッ　美也ちゃん
今日もかわいいわね
Miya-chan, you're cute, as always!
美也？
ありゃりゃ？
M-Miya?
先に行く
Oh?
See you later.
美也！　すみません先輩
Miya!
I'm sorry, Senpai.
う～ん　ホントに猫ちゃんみたい
She really is like a kitten.
いつかきっと
仲良くなってみせるわ
I'll definitely become friends with her someday!
美也　何だよ　あの態度は
Miya, what's with that attitude?
You were also like this the last time.  It's rude!
この前もそうだけど失礼だろ
Do you dislike Morishima-senpai?
森島先輩のこと嫌いなのか？
先輩すごく…
She really likes-
うるさい　そんなの分かってるよ！
Shut up!
I know that much!
じゃあ何だよ？
話しかけても返事もしないくせに
What's wrong, then?
You don't even respond to me when I talk to you,
森島先輩が来たとたんニヤニヤしてさ
ニヤニヤって…
but when Morishima-senpai comes along, you keep grinning and...
Grin?
えいッ！
うッ！
（梅原）おッ
水もしたたる　いい男だね
Ooh, you're dripping wet and incredibly handsome!
今度は　どうしたの？
What happened this time?
（麻耶）１６００年　関ヶ原の戦いに
勝利した徳川家康は→
In the year 1600, Tokugawa Ieyasu won the Battle of Sekigahara and received the title of Shogun in the year 1603...
１６０３年　征夷大将軍に…
Grinning?
〈ニヤニヤか…
してたかもしれないな〉
Maybe I was.
あッ　うん？
You
look
retarded
あッ
・（麻耶）やめなさい　二人とも！
Cut it out, both of you!
まったく　薫のヤツ　先生からバツ
として掃除当番って言われたのに
Damn that Kaoru.
Saying she has a part-time job and going home after the teacher said that we'd be punished with cleaning duty.
バイトがあるとか言って
さっさと帰りやがって…
I'll definitely pay her back...
今度　何か　おごらせよう
（はるか）橘君！
Tachibana-kun!
Morishima-senpai.
森島先輩
女子用の水着持ってない？
Good timing!
Do you happen to have a girl's swimsuit?
はッ？
だから　女子用の水着！
I said, a girl's swimsuit!
There's no way I'd have one.
持ってるワケないじゃないですか
もしかしたらと思ったんだけど
I see, I thought you might've had one...
持ってたら逆に危ないですよ
美也ちゃんのでもいいんだけど
It'd be creepy if I did have one.
I know!  Why don't I take Miya-chan's swimsuit?
どうするつもりですか？
着るに決まってるじゃない
What are you going to do with Miya's swimsuit?
I'm gonna wear it, obviously.
Miya's swimsuit?
美也のをですか？
イエス！
Yes!
いやいや　ダメですよ
先輩が美也の水着なんて着たら
No no no, it won't work.
It'd be pretty bad if you tried to wear Miya's swimsuit.
大変なことになっちゃいます
そうかな～
Really?
でも　どうして
急に水着なんです？
Though, why do you suddenly need a swimsuit?
Well, after seeing the Swim Club do their training,
何かね
水泳部の練習をのぞいていたら
私も泳ぎたくなっちゃった
I felt like swimming too.
ああ
そういうことだったんですね
So that's why.
そうだ　水泳部の子に
お願いしてみようかな
I know!  Should I ask one of the girls in the Swim Club?
えッ　でも…
大丈夫
Huh?  But...
It'll be fine.
I don't think they use their usual
school swimsuits during their training.
学校指定の水着は
部活では使わないと思うの
Really?
ですかね？
よ～し　プールに突撃よ
All right, time to invade the pool!
ゴーゴーゴー！
えッ　ちょっと先輩？
Go go go!
W-Wait, Senpai?!
Huh?!  Y-You want my swimsuit?
（女子部員）私の水着ですか？
（はるか）そう
That's right.
これを？
それじゃなくて
You want this?
Not that, your usual school swimsuit is fine.
学校指定の水着でいいの
少しでいいから貸してくれない？
It's only gonna be for a bit, so could you lend it to me?
はい…　それならいいですよ
Okay... I'm fine with that.
オーキードーキー　ありがとう！
じゃあ着替えてくるわね
Okie dokie, thanks!
Well then, I'm gonna get changed!
ちょっ…　先輩
Wait, S... Senpai!
（小声で）何でゴミ箱…
（小声で）やだ～
Why is there a guy here?
（逢）どうして
ここに男子がいるんですか？
この時間は
女子水泳部の活動中ですよ
This is when the Girls Swim Club has its practice.
What do you think you're doing?
何をしているんですか？
違うんだ
I-It's not what you think!
これには事情が…
ゴミ捨て場と間違えたという
There's an explanation for this...
You're saying you mistook this place for the rubbish dump?
言い訳ですか？
あッ　いや…
Ah, no...
これも　いろいろあって…
・（はるか）お待たせ～
There's also an explanation for this...
Sorry I took so long!
どう？　似合う？
Well?
Does it look good?
O-Of course!
もちろんです
ありがと
Thanks.
森島先輩
あら逢ちゃん　偶然ね
Morishima-senpai.
Ooh, Ai-chan.  What a coincidence.
どう？　似合う？
この人　お知り合いですか？
Well, does it look good?
Senpai, do you know him?
うん　２年生の橘純一君
どうも…
Yep.  He's Tachibana Junichi-kun, a junior.
H-Hello.
And she's Nanasaki Ai-chan, a freshman.
・（はるか）
こっちが１年の七咲逢ちゃん
I'm Nanasaki Ai.
七咲逢です
じゃ　お互い紹介もすんだことだし
Now that you've been introduced to each other, it's time to swim!
さッ　泳ぐわよ～！　あッ
（逢）部長
（響）騒がしいと思って来たら→
President.
I come to see what's causing all the commotion, and I find two outsiders.
部外者が二人も
響ちゃん　お願い→
Hibiki-chan, please.
Let me swim just for a bit.
ちょっとだけでいいから泳がせて
（響）ダメ
No.
Don't be such a spoilsport.
そんな　つれないこと言わないで
・（響）ダメなものはダメ
No means no.
Non-club members aren't allowed in here.
部外者は立ち入り禁止よ
着替えてさっさと出ていって
Get changed and get out of here.
Come on...
そんな～
チェッ…
橘君もね
Tachibana-kun, you too.
はッ　はい
O-Okay.
Geez, Hibiki-chan's so stingy.
（はるか）
もう　響ちゃんのケチんぼ！
She didn't have a choice.
仕方ないですよ　塚原先輩にも
部長っていう立場がありますから
Tsukahara-senpai has her own duties as club president.
What?  You're on Hibiki's side?
何よ　響の味方するつもり？
I didn't mean it that way...
そういうワケじゃないですけど
あッ　そうだ先輩　図書室行って
Ah, I know!
Why don't we go to the library and look at some photo albums of puppies?
また子犬の写真集でも見ませんか
気分転換に
It'll cheer you up.
え～ッ　でも
この前　結構　借りちゃったからな
Huh?  But I already borrowed most of them recently.
まだ　かわいい本あるかな？
大丈夫ですよ　きっとまだ
I wonder if they have other books with cute things in them?
Don't worry, I'm sure there are
other books we haven't found yet.
見つけてない本が
僕が探し出してみせます
I'll find them for you.
Really?
ホントに？
オッケー　じゃあ行くわよ
Yes.
Okay!  Then let's go!
Make sure you find an awesome book!
素敵な本を見つけてね
任せてください
Gotcha!  Leave it to me!
All right, let's go!
（はるか）それじゃ　レッツゴー！
その前にゴミ箱だけでも教室に
S-Senpai, at least let me drop off this dustbin at the classroom...
Well then, I'll go and look.
じゃあ　探してきます
うん　待ってるわね
Yep, I'll be waiting.
梨穂子？
（梨穂子）うん？　純一！？
Rihoko?
Junichi?!
Why are you here?
どうして　ここに？
どうしてって
Why, you ask?
本を探しに来たんだよ
そうだよね　図書室だもんね
I'm here to look for a book.
I see.  This is a library, after all...
お前　何を隠してるんだ？
What are you hiding?
Let's see...
う～んと…　ダイエットの本
A book on dieting.
うわッ　何で分かるの？
H-How did you know?
何年　幼なじみやってると
思ってるんだよ
We've been friends since childhood.
梨穂子ならダイエットか
料理の本しかないと思ってね
I'm pretty sure you'd only go for books on dieting and cooking, Rihoko.
はあ～ッ　どうせ「また」とか
思ってるんでしょう
You must be thinking that I'm trying again , right?
Well, I did see you repeatedly fail at dieting since middle school.
中学の頃から何度もダイエットに
失敗しているの見ているからな～
どうせ今度も…
いじわる
You'll probably fail again.
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Meanie.
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
そんなに気にするほどでも
ないけど
I don't think you need to be that worried about dieting.
えッ？
まあ　頑張れよ
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Only 10 minutes a day!!
Mini-Exercise Diet
You can still eat what you want!
Anyway, good luck.
あッ…　うん
Ah...
Okay!
I couldn't really find that many...
あんまり見つからなかったな…
うん？
う～ん　ううん…
おはようございます　先輩
Wakey wakey, Senpai.
ああ…　ゴメンね　寝ちゃった
I'm sorry, I fell asleep.
少しだけです
あッ　かけてくれたんだ
Only for a bit.
Ah, you put it on me.
Thanks.  You're nice.
ありがと　優しいね
いえ　そんな…
No problem...
（せきばらい）
すみません　それだけしか
見つけられませんでした
I'm sorry.  These were all I could find.
ううん　ありがとう
あッ　これ　まだ見てない
It's fine, thanks.
Ah, I haven't seen this one yet!
これも　これも　やるわね～
This one, or this one either!
Good job!
それほどでも…
It was nothing.
わ～ッ　これ　かわいい
この写真もキュート　フフフ…
This is so adorable!
This picture's cute too!
Senpai.
先輩
うん？
好きです
えッ？
I like you.
Huh?
I like you, Morishima-senpai.
僕　森島先輩が好きです
もう…　またなの？
すみません
Geez, again?
Sorry.
迷惑なら　もう二度と
こんなことを言いません
If it bothers you, I'll never say it again.
It doesn't bother me, but...
迷惑じゃないけど…　何で？
Why?
一緒にいると楽しくて　もっと
いろいろな話をしたいというか
I have so much fun when I'm with you.
It's like, I want to talk to you about all kinds of stuff, and...
それで…
急にそんなこと言って…
That was unexpected...
すみません
謝らないで
Sorry.
Don't apologize.
すみま…　あッ
Sorr- Ah.
Why?  I mean, I already...
何で？　だって　この間…
諦めたくなくて…
先輩が迷惑じゃなくて
I couldn't give up.
You said you weren't bothered by it, so I didn't want to give up if I could have another chance.
またチャンスが　もらえるなら
諦めたくない
何度フラれても構わない
I don't care how many times you reject me.
What I'm most afraid of is being unable to even get a reply.
僕が一番怖いのは
返事さえもらえないことなので
そんなことしないわ
ありがとうございます
I-I wouldn't do that.
Thank you.
何　お礼言ってるの…　変なの
W-Why are you thanking me?  You're weird.
Um...
あの…　僕　先輩のこと
好きでいていいですか？
Is it okay if I continue to like you?
うっとうしかったら諦めます
If it annoys you, I'll stop.
うっとうしくなんかない…
It doesn't annoy me...
じゃあ　いいんですか？
Then... you don't mind?
うん
やった　ありがとうございます！
No.
Yay!  Thank you so much!
もう…
えッ？
Geez...
Huh?
Geez, why do you try so hard?
もう　何でそんなに一生懸命かな
If you try that hard...
そんなに頑張られたら…
I can't just say no...
ほっとけないじゃない
先輩？
もう
Senpai?
Geez.
これでも食らえ！
Take this!
えッ　今の…
Huh?  W-What was that...?
必死で八の字になってる
君の困りまゆ毛が
Your eyebrows were furrowed from trying so hard.
あんまり
かわいいからキスしたの
They were kinda cute, so I kissed them.
See you later!
またね
・～
Kawaii sore dake de
かわいいそれだけで
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
夢中で撫でたくなる潤んだ瞳
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
じゃれている時は
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
なついているだけだと
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
思ってたんだ
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
恋の始まりなんて
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
予報外れの天気みたい
is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
雨上がりの虹の空に手伸ばそう
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
君の隣は素直な
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
気持ちになれるから
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
気付いた君の事想う
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
時間は胸の奥がこんなに高鳴る事
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
昨日夢の中に
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
また君が出てきた
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview!
What's the matter, Nii-nii?
You're surprisingly upbeat today.
Miya, you have no idea just how happy I am right now!
Huh?  Just how happy are you?
I'm pretty happy if I can have my meat buns,
but you're happier than that?
Happier than if you got twenty meat buns!
What?!  You're that happy?!
Next Episode: "Jealousy".
Next Episode
Jealousy
I feel bad for you, Nii-nii.
You've pretty much used up all your happiness in this life.
Don't say such ominous things!